>> Okay. We can use hypothesis testing to see
好了 我们现在能够使用假设检验确定
whether a difference we observe in our experiment is actually significant.
确定实验中观察到的差异是否具有统计显著性
What comes next?
那接下来呢？
>> So what we have to do next is decide from a business perspective, what change
我们接下来需要从商业角度来决定
in the click-through probability ability is practically significant.
怎样的点击概率变化具有实际显著性
In other words, what size change matters to us?
也就是说 变更对我们来说有多重要
>> Well, as a statistician would say,
作为统计学家来讲
what's substantive in addition to being statistically significant.
这是统计显著性以外的实质性
>> That's the difference between what engineers say and
这就是工程师与统计学家
what statisticians say.
的不同说法了
Substantive and practically significant mean the exact same thing.
实质性与实际显著性其实是指一样的东西
>> Okay.
好的
So why can't we say that every change matters to the business?
为什么我们不认为在商业上所有变更都比较重要？
Can't we launch any experiment that makes any difference at all?
我们不能进行任何能够造成差别的实验么？
>> Well, you could, but you might not want to for a variety of reasons.
你可以 但是你可能不想这么做 这有多个原因
One, there might be an investment in making the change itself, so
首先 变更本身可能是需要投资的
it might not be worth it to you or you might just want to wait for the next
可能你觉得并不值得 或者说你想要等下一次变更
change, thinking that maybe you could do well here, but you could do better.
觉得这里变更会不错 但是那样做会更好
So, in something like medicine,
比如在医学方面
you always want to be clear that it's worth the change.
你必须清楚知道变更是否值得
If you're testing a new drug, maybe patient's respond a little bit better,
如果你在测试一种新药 可能病人的反应会稍微好一点
but you're going to have to invest in training nurses,
但你必须要投资用来培训护士
actually launching the drug.
才能实际推出这种药
All these other things.
诸如此类的
So you may want to have a higher level of practical significance to justify
所以你可能需要更高的实际显著性
changing the treatment protocol.
才变更治疗方案
>> Now this is one major difference between the online world and
这个也是网络世界和传统科学
sort of the traditional sciences, right?
之间的重大差异之一 对吧？
In medicine, you probably want a 5%, a 10%,
在医学中 5%、10%
a 15% change to really be substantive.
15% 的变更才是实质性的
Right? At Google, for example,
对吧？ 但是比如说 在 Google
a 1 or a 2% change in click-through probabilities is actually quite large.
点击概率里的1%或者2%的改变就已经很大了
And so the differences in the magnitudes for
所以被认为具有实际显著性的差异
what's consider practically significant can be quite different.
也是非常不同的
>> Yeah, so what you really want to observe is repeatability.
是的 所以你真正关注的应该是可重复性
Statistical significance is about repeatability.
统计显著性讨论的就是可重复性
>> And you want to make sure when you setup your experiment that you get that
所以在你设置实验时 你想要确保
guarantee that yes, these results are repeatable so
对的 这些结果是可重复的
it's statistically significant.
那它就具有统计显著性
But you also want to make sure that if you see a change in your experiment that
但你还需要确认从商业角度来说
you're interested in from a business standpoint, so
你在实验中也看到了你感兴趣的改变
it's practically significant, it's also statistically significant.
它就具有实际显著性 也具有统计显著性
So you want to size your experiment appropriately, such that the statistical
所以你要恰当地设计实验的规模
significance bar is actually lower than the practical significance bar.
确保统计显著性条柱低于实际显著性条柱
>> That makes sense.
有道理
So then, so the audacity example,
那在 Audacity 的例子中
we still need to pick a practical significance boundary.
我们仍需要选一个实际显著性的边界
>> That's right.
对的
So let's say that from a business perspective, a 2%
比如说 从商业角度来说
change in the click-through probability would be practically significant.
2%的点击概率改变就具有实际显著性